On April 23rd,
Prince William and his wife Kate have welcomed their third child.
Louis Arthur Charles,
a boy weighing 3.8 kilograms, fifth in line to the throne.
Very happy, delighted, thank you. Three, three times more worried now.
On May 19th, his brother, Prince Harry, will marry his fiancée Meghan Markle.
This rather unexpected marriage,
It's wonderful, it's a surprise, let's go, at full speed.
By finding love,
The two princes seem to have never been happier than they are today.
We cherish them, William and Harry.
They are part of our daily lives.
They were determined to make their private lives a success, and to make their upcoming marriage a success.
This is how this monarchy feeds and perpetuates itself.
Who is Meghan Markle and how did she meet Harry?
Please welcome the lovely Meghan Markle.
How did this American woman, a commoner, divorced, and of mixed race,
Did she convince the queen to allow their marriage?
She is anything but the young girl who was raised to one day become the companion of one of the princes of England, quite the contrary.
She is a woman who sets an example of something that I believe is very important.
Today, the barriers and boundaries of love go beyond everything.
When you love, you can.
And she succeeded.
Why are people already saying that Kate and Meghan hate each other?
Are they pretending to like each other?
Kate needs to maintain her position, and that's not easy with someone new coming in.
She comes from two different worlds,
They are two parallel worlds, after all.
One is formatted for,
The other one wasn't part of the plan.
Why is Harry the royal family's favorite prince?
Harry, after all those difficult years, has finally become the most popular member of the royal family.
Even in front of the Queen, it's still quite an achievement.
How is William experiencing this situation?
Does he really want to become king?
William is the reason.
Perhaps a thoughtful person, someone who won't cross the line.
William is ready to be king, but would he want to be?
We cannot decide it, but he has been prepared for this role.
For a long time, the lives of the two brothers were nothing but drama and scandal.
They were born in palaces destined to become kings.
And at the same time, they experienced the most human tragedy. They lost their mother when they were very young.
On August 31, 1997,
Princess Diana died in a tragic car accident in Paris.
leaving Harry and William orphans.
Why did William refuse to attend his mother's funeral?
And how did he change his mind?
They would have liked to be alone, with their conscience, with their memory, with their tenderness for their mother, but it was impossible.
How did Prince Harry rebuild his life after his mother's death?
Why did he fall into severe depressions?
Harry is his mother's baby.
And so, when Harry becomes an orphan, when he loses his mother,
His world is completely collapsing.
How did the two princes cope with the loss of their mother?
It has been a difficult fate,
But ultimately, they were able to overcome this difficult moment and find the strength.
For 20 years, the two princes have replaced Diana, the people's princess, in the hearts of the British.
So, who are William and Harry really?
November 27, 2017,
Prince Harry creates a surprise.
After only a year and a half of relationship,
He announced his engagement in front of about a hundred journalists.
summoned that very morning to the gardens of Kensington Palace.
Prince, how did the proposal go?
It was an unforgettable evening.
Was it romantic?
Of course it was.
The fact that I fell in love with Megan incredibly quickly,
It was confirmation for me that all the stars were aligned, that everything was just perfect.
We are a fantastic team, we are sure of it.
I'm very excited about all of this.
Everything is perfect.
The news, relayed by television stations around the world, had the effect of an earthquake.
Prince Harry has announced his marriage to American actress Meghan Markle.
Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are engaged, we're going to have an American princess.
At 33, Harry, the most sought-after prince on the planet, has finally found the woman of his life.
This is the event we've been waiting for for years.
We were beginning to despair that this eternal bachelor would ever settle down.
The women must have cried because they had to say, "It's over, we can no longer marry Cinderella's Prince Charming."
The lucky woman chosen is Meghan Markle.
She's gorgeous, Meghan, she's absolutely stunning.
I don't think Harry is bored.
I think she's wonderful, she's very beautiful.
And besides, she's a woman...
She is a woman of her time.
Virtually unknown in Europe just a year ago,
Now the future princess causes a riot every time she goes out.
Gently, gently, step back. One step backward.
There's a kind of Meghan mania that developed in an incredible amount of time. I mean, very, very quickly, she became one of the most famous women on the planet.
Meghan is a dream come true because she is a young girl who comes from a modest background and is going to be in the most famous and most photographed family in the world.
Please welcome the lovely Meghan Markle.
Hello Meghan, you look magnificent.
However, on paper...
Meghan Markle,
36 years old,
who is a commoner,
American,
Being mixed race, an actress, divorced and older than Harry, she has nothing to appeal to the royal family.
She's the anti-English princess when you look at her destiny.
Actress,
That's not what they prefer.
The fact that she was divorced didn't sit well with the Queen of England. She doesn't fit into any category.
Enough to make you choke on your scones at Buckingham Palace.
Young people today think it's fantastic. An American actress who seems quite wild. And then Prince Harry, who himself was a bad boy.
They are both the elixir of transgression.
So they bring a little bit of madness.
Faced with Harry's determination to marry Meghan,
Queen Elizabeth II authorized this union, which was unthinkable just a few years ago.
The fact that Queen Elizabeth approves of Harry's marriage to this young woman
who is not from the aristocracy, not even English,
It's a step towards modernity.
It's a respect for the love of these two young people and breaking with the old, somewhat dusty aristocratic tradition; it also makes it a little more rock'n'roll.
And Elizabeth II has not finished surprising these subjects.
For Christmas, she invited Meghan Markle to join the Windsors.
a privilege to which no fiancée in the family had ever been entitled.
Meghan was lucky enough to spend Christmas with the Queen.
It had never been done before. So the whole country, British citizens, thought, "Ah, times are changing, that's funny."
The ceremony will take place on May 19th at Windsor Castle, the Queen's favorite country residence, 40 km from London.
A fortress almost 1000 years old,
steeped in history for the royal family.
It's important to understand that this is an extraordinary gift.
that the sovereign does because of the Royal Chapel of St. George at Windsor,
It's an exceptional place.
This is where Harry was baptized in 1984. So it's a place full of symbolism and memories for him.
We are very close to London.
But at the same time, we're not in the heart of the city because Harry isn't the heir to the throne, he's just his little brother.
Just like Kate Middleton seven years ago,
Meghan's every move is being scrutinized to try and uncover details about this ultra-secret wedding.
I'm sure Meghan is already having sleepless nights.
Because it's difficult.
When you're organizing a thousand things, and you have a thousand guests, you can't forget anything.
Meghan Markle must leave nothing to chance.
starting with her wedding dress, which will be the focus of everyone's attention on the day of the ceremony.
But one question is on everyone's lips.
Will this dress make her a princess?
The actress felt like she'd seen it all before.
seen wearing white in an episode of Suits.
the series that brought him to the public's attention.
We can easily imagine that she's not going to get married in a leather jacket with a mini-skirt.
That's unthinkable for a member of the royal family.
Nevertheless, she has a say in things and she has always had a strong character.
So we can indeed expect a little twist, a little touch of originality from him.
Rumors suggest Meghan Markle will spend 450,000 euros on her wedding dress.
one of the biggest expenses of the wedding.
So there are a few stylists who have already been considered.
There is a lot of talk about a certain Misha Nonoo, who is a great friend of Meghan Markle, who has notably already dressed her on the sets of the series Suits.
There is also Jessica Mulroney, who is of Canadian origin and who dresses, among others, the young wife of Justin Trudeau, the Canadian Prime Minister.
And to make a lasting impression, Meghan Markle could also challenge religious traditions because of her family.
We know she is very, very close to her mother.
On the other hand, she has a slightly more distant relationship with her father, Thomas.
Raised by her mother after her parents' divorce,
Meghan rarely sees her father, who lives in Mexico, reclusive and penniless.
One of the latest rumors says that she asked her mother to accompany her to the hotel and not her father.
So that breaks with tradition.
but it's also about being respected as a woman in her choices.
She sets the tone, she sets the tone very quickly and this suggests an energetic young woman who will very, very successfully forge her path in the royal family.
On the guest side, the future bride and groom would also like to create a surprise.
with a garden that was much more glittery than regal.
Meghan is no longer an actress on Suits, but she has remained very good friends with many of her co-stars, so we can hope to see some of them.
She is also friends with Serena Williams, the tennis champion.
We know that Harry is really good friends with Barack Obama.
I can interview you if you want?
No, no, let's do it as planned. I'm more comfortable this way.
But neither Barack Obama nor the current US president, Donald Trump, will be present.
Harry is only sixth in line to the throne.
They will at least receive an invitation.
The entire global elite dreams of getting an invitation.
But only 600 privileged people will have the right to attend the ceremony.
A marriage, which is also sparking the wildest rumors.
The most incredible thing is the return of the Spice Girls, the famous English girl band.
All this speculation is a boon for London bookmakers.
If the number one sport in England is polo, the second is probably betting.
And it is true that even now, bookmakers are having a field day.
Will Prince Harry wear a beard on his wedding day, yes or no?
Will Meghan Markle wear a tiara, yes or no, and which one?
The taste of the cake,
the wedding theme or the name of Meghan's maid of honor.
All these bets are stirring up passions.
The royal family had not generated such enthusiasm since the birth of Kate and William's children.
It's a boy, it's a big baby.
A much-anticipated resurgence of interest,
since this royal wedding could bring nearly 600 million euros to the British economy.
The monarchy is also profitable.
Every time there's a wedding in England, inevitably there are tourists, they sell merchandise, you know, improbable biscuit tins, objects more kitschy than the next.
The English love it.
These royal weddings, it's really...
a breath of fresh air for the British.
As you said,
Now is the time to build our future together.
We're only at the beginning.
There is a lot to do, a lot to do.
By marrying Meghan Markle, Prince Harry is bringing a smile back to the monarchy, just like William before him.
The two brothers, always side by side, are more united than ever.
Prince Harry has such a close relationship with his older brother William,
They experienced so much together that it bonded them as children.
that they could not ignore.
Prince Harry's best man will be his older brother.
Harry and William seem to have finally turned the page on the greatest tragedy of their lives.
The nightmare of William and his brother Harry began on August 31, 1997.
Everyone is in shock, there is a wave of shock.
I thought it was a joke, I said it's not possible, she's too young.
This type of person does not die.
This is one of the great tragedies of the British monarchy.
It was completely unpredictable.
an accident that has shocked global public opinion.
an icon.
It was an injustice to her, she didn't deserve it, she was the people's princess.
Then we immediately think of William and Harry.
At the time of the tragedy, William, 15, and Harry, 12, were on holiday at Balmoral Castle in Scotland with the Queen and their father.
We know that it was Prince Charles who was personally woken up on Sunday to announce the news to them.
And they have absolutely touching and incredibly moving words when they talk about those moments, saying "we didn't understand, we didn't really understand".
The death of their mother is obviously like heaven and earth collapsing.
Elizabeth II, their grandmother,
will then do everything to protect them from the media frenzy that is starting in London.
The emotion was global. I think I would even use the word global hysteria rather than global emotion.
It was insane.
The Queen's first reaction when she learned of it a little while earlier was to say to immediately remove the radios and televisions from the palace.
The queen desperately tried to be a grandmother,
to protect his grandsons.
She wanted them to have a few days at Balmoral, just to come to terms with this terrible news.
If the queen wants to cut the two princes off from the rest of the world,
It's because she herself has already experienced such a tragedy.
The sudden death of his father, George VI, in 1952,
when she was 25 years old.
Elisabeth knew exactly what she was doing.
She herself learned of her father's death while she was traveling.
She left England as a princess, she returned as a queen.
and the media frenzy,
She knows what it's like to suffer from it, and she didn't want to impose it on her grandsons, who were so young and so fragile.
Despite the Queen's efforts, the fervor surrounding Diana is gaining ground at Balmoral and will hit the two princes hard.
The day after receiving the news, they nevertheless attended a mass near Balmoral, where they were forced to see people,
to see little notes, to see flowers.
Harry says this rather shocking thing.
He said that he himself could not cry, but that the people who touched him had hands wet with their own tears.
The two brothers are all the more devastated by grief as they cannot stop thinking about their last conversation with their mother Diana.
A phone call that took place a few hours before the tragedy.
They are playing with their cousins ​​in the garden, the weather is nice, it's great, it's summer.
She calls from Paris, says she will be back the next day and tells them, among other things, that she has found them some lovely and beautiful gifts.
And in fact, they shorten this phone call a little bit.
Mom, let's go back to playing, everything's fine for you, great, see you in a few days.
For 20 years, Harry and William have regretted the casual attitude they had towards their mother on that tragic day.
This last conversation really haunted them because, obviously, they couldn't have known it would be the last.
They were deeply hurt to realize they should have paid more attention to her, been more present.
take more time.
William and Harry spend 6 dreadful days at Balmoral.
But they are unaware that an even more shocking ordeal awaits them upon their return to London.
Their mother's state funeral.
Diana's funeral was a major trauma for her two brothers. It was an absolutely terrible time for them.
And that was truly overwhelming, an image that shook all of England.
On September 6, 1997,
William and Harry, who have become the most famous orphans on the planet,
find themselves exposed in front of cameras from all over the world.
When you see them behind, following their mother's coffin...
That's still the most moving thing, though.
They possess an incredible, incredible dignity.
How come they don't sob? How do they manage? In the evening, when we get home, we imagine them collapsed in their beds, crying into their pillows.
At that moment, they embodied the royal side of the family, meaning they were straightforward and never showed anything. It truly reflected the queen's motto: "Never explain, never complain."
Two and a half billion viewers in 180 countries are watching these poignant images, and wondering about the letter seen on a bed of lilies.
Diana's favorite flowers.
I'm thinking of the thing that moved us the most; it was the word "Mum" written on the bag by Prince Harry.
We all wanted to take him in our arms and say, "Poor little boy, his mother has died,
He is going through an ordeal that no one wants to experience.
Harry and his brother William do not crack.
However, just a few days earlier, they categorically refused to participate in this procession.
It's already terrible enough to have lost your mother, so to experience your grief during a 30-minute procession through the capital, with billions of people watching and scrutinizing us on television,
Can you imagine how terrible this is? It's a burden for these children.
They would have liked to be alone with their conscience, with their memory, with their tenderness for their mother, but it was impossible.
It is Prince Philip, the Queen's husband and grandfather of the two boys,
who will convince William to take his place in the procession.
It was really his grandfather, the Duke of Edinburgh, who said to him, "What if I come with you? What if I am with you?"
And then, all of a sudden, William really felt the whole family reunited.
He will say to himself, "Diana performed a miracle beyond death."
That is to say, she reconciles a family that was torn apart, and his normal place is to walk behind her.
Supported by their grandfather and their father, Prince Charles,
The boys will walk with their heads down almost 2 kilometers behind their mother's coffin.
Dignified and stoic.
They earn the respect and affection of an entire people.
It's part of their duty, in a way, but at 15, 12 years old, you don't get to choose.
I think it was extremely violent, and that's why we have so much sympathy for Harry and William today.
William hides behind his lock of hair.
Like Diana, with her famous look from beneath her fringe. He tries to shield himself from the stares of millions of people.
Harry, even more fragile,
He said it was the biggest shock of his life.
He felt it was wrong to ask a child to do that, and that today, he believes it wouldn't be done anymore.
And the emotion will rise even further during the religious ceremony at Westminster Abbey.
when Elton John sits down at the piano to pay tribute to his friend Diana.
Candle in the Wind, by Elton John,
That was probably the most moving moment.
Since he was one of Diana's best friends,
And yes, there was so much emotion in her voice, there was so much sadness.
It was a moment when everyone cried.
Even in the royal court, we see people crying.
I was watching television and crying.
And I was thinking, they don't even have the right to cry.
There were flashes of light on the two children who were unaware.
Prince Harry would later confide, "That was the only time I really thought I was going to break down."
I had promised Mom I wouldn't cry. At that moment, I almost did.
Having endured the ordeal of the funeral,
Harry must learn to live without his mother, whom he cherished.
He doesn't yet know that this will be the toughest fight of his life.
Harry is his mother's baby.
And so, when Harry becomes an orphan,
When he loses his mother, his world completely collapses.
He can't believe what's happening to him.
That seems inconceivable.
He will say and repeat that in order not to suffer, he had to not think about his mother.
Harry suffered terribly.
He said it recently, he confided in us. He did, after all, go through some very violent depressive episodes.
He really came close at times.
to lose common sense.
Harry spoke about this trauma for the first time only a few months ago on the radio.
I can calmly say that losing my mother at 12 years old and consequently blocking all my emotions for the last 20 years.
This has had serious consequences, not only on my personal life, but also in my work.
The young prince speaks of it discreetly.
But in reality,
The lost teenager experienced a long descent into hell.
After his mother's funeral,
William will give the impression of handling grief much better than his brother.
He resumes his life as a high school student at Eton.
William, for his part, showed no sign of it. He was 15 years old, and he continued to pursue his studies.
All around him, he has both teachers and classmates who support him and are by his side. He is integrated into something that will protect him and act as a kind of cocoon.
In reality, if William doesn't succumb, it's because he has no choice.
He is the eldest and future king,
and he has no right to feel sorry for himself.
William is the reason.
the mastermind,
the one who will not cross the line.
His path is chosen.
He does not have the freedom to refuse it.
He must get a good education, he must learn his job as king.
It's easier for William, he has a crutch.
This crutch is quite strong; it's the crown.
He knows where he needs to go.
From the moment he was born, William was programmed to be exemplary in every way.
At that time, after his mother's death, William became more aware than ever of his role and place within the royal family.
During his last three years of boarding school at Eton,
That's Elisabeth, his grandmother.
who will be responsible for teaching him his future role as king.
His grandmother receives him at least one afternoon a week, perhaps more often.
The queen knows this all too well.
Being a king is not something you can just improvise.
She explains to him both her experience and memories, and what he can expect as king. She essentially gives him a lesson, drawing on the experience of over 60 years of reign.
At 18, in memory of his mother, William spent three months in Chile on a community and ecological project.
I wanted to do something constructive this year.
I really needed to feel useful.
I felt I needed to help people in need.
and that I encounter different populations from around the world.
It's the idea of ​​being able to have a normal life. It's almost a mantra for William, meaning he repeats it constantly.
This is even the first time that a future king of England has been filmed to this extent in his private life.
We see Prince William, for example, cleaning toilets in a center for neglected children.
There is this extremely strong desire, totally inherited from Diana, to be close to people.
Hi, it's Will.
Unable to bear the excessive media attention he has been subjected to since the death of his mother, Lady Diana,
William breaks with 150 years of tradition by choosing to attend the university of his choice.
It will be a matter of choosing the University of St Andrews, which is not at all a university attended by members of the royal family.
He chose discretion and, above all, distance from the media.
Since his mother's death, he wants to be in a more discreet place.
When this unexpected choice is announced, applications for female registration skyrocket.
Among the contenders was a certain Kate Middleton.
That year, enrollments increased by 44%. Many girls wanted to attend university, and Kate Middleton was one of them.
By joining this faculty, Kate secretly hopes to be able to get her hands on the most eligible bachelor in England.
She went to the same university because she wanted to catch him.
She wanted to go out with him.
It was far from certain that she would go further than just a quick encounter.
From a very young age, the young woman dreamed of marrying William and becoming a princess.
From a very young age, at school, she had a fondness for the royal family. She always loved it.
She already had a poster of William in her room.
She always wanted to become a princess, ever since she was very young.
and to marry Prince William.
Urged on by her family, she does everything to seduce the young prince.
It was like a bomb sent by the family to catch the future king of England.
On March 27, 2002,
At a charity fashion show, Kate will finally achieve her goal.
She thought to herself, William will be there, I have to get his attention.
So she wore a rather transparent dress.
which had an immediate effect.
And there, she goes from being an intelligent, nice, serious girl,
to the sexy girl.
William reportedly said, "Wow, Kate, that's hot."
It was love at first sight.
It was that evening that the couple shared their first kiss and began a serious relationship.
However, Kate doesn't really fit the profile of the ideal princess.
Coming from a working-class background,
She is not part of the aristocracy.
She is a truck driver, she is the daughter of Michael and Carol Middleton.
His parents were fairly normal people who genuinely wanted to rise in society.
Ambitious, his parents, former employees of an airline, made their fortune in party supplies.
They are a lower-middle-class family, if you will, until he creates this party accessories company that makes them what we call the nouveau riche.
The Middleton family represents the "self-made man" type who succeeds and climbs the social ladder. It's a waking dream.
For William, who suffered from his parents' divorce and the death of his mother when he was 15,
The Middletons are a blessing.
Prince William has found a sense of normalcy again in the Middletons.
normality, a united family, a healthy family, a stable family.
It was something he had never experienced and something he truly longed for.
William discovers something as natural as being able to eat breakfast in his pajamas.
a simplicity he had often dreamed of.
Kate's parents really did serve as surrogate parents for William at one point. He spent Christmases with them.
He is extraordinarily happy at his in-laws' house. He has spent entire weekends there rather than going to his grandmother's palaces.
Now that William has finally found the warmth of a home,
His brother Harry is spiraling into hell.
Early January 2005,
The darling of the English commits the irreparable.
Harry is photographed wearing a swastika at a masked ball.
The image has scandalized the entire world.
When these photos are published in the press, they create a terrible buzz, a terrible bad buzz.
It brings back terrible memories.
England having been threatened with destruction by the Germans and by Hitler.
We are 15 days away from the commemorations of the Jewish Holocaust which are to be celebrated in London.
This is going to cause quite a stir in England and the whole world.
Since the death of his mother 8 years earlier,
Harry is adrift.
Every evening, after classes, as a remedy for grief,
He found nothing but alcohol, drugs, and sleepless nights.
Very soon, the particularly boozy evenings will begin. The prince loves gin.
But there is also a little more than alcohol, there are drugs circulating as well.
Harry is not a saint, he's a gossip.
He's definitely the bad boy of the family.
A life of debauchery that makes him completely forget that he is constantly followed by a horde of paparazzi.
He is the only member of the royal family who has been seen staggering out of a club to the point where he almost fell.
Also remember that he was nicknamed: Harry Pothead.
Obviously a play on words with Harry Potter because people said he smoked joints, etc.
He is also the only prince photographed naked.
As in this suite of hotels in Las Vegas in the company of several young women who were also undressed.
This was a second major breach, we might say, of his role as a member of the royal family.
This is the famous strip poker in Las Vegas.
He completely lets loose, we find him naked, it's not a big deal.
The problem is that there's always someone around him ready to spill the beans.
Harry never forgot how journalists harassed his mother until her tragic death.
On October 22, 2004,
that night,
That's one flash too many.
And Harry is going to go crazy.
It's going to escalate to physical violence; he's capable of becoming violent in these kinds of circumstances.
The prince doesn't hesitate to hit a few paparazzi who want some private photos.
Even if it goes further and further,
The British people remain exceptionally lenient with Harry.
her little orphaned prince.
He is suffering, this is his way of reacting.
He is in rebellion.
Yes, we forgive him everything.
The British people love to hear about his antics, his moments of madness.
It makes him more human.
If Harry can get away with anything, it's also because he's the second oldest in the family.
A position that protects him and allows him to be himself.
Harry will never ascend the throne. He doesn't have the position or the pressure that William has.
He's not the oldest, he's the youngest, so we have the opportunity to do more silly things, I think.
This is a completely fundamental trait in Harry's personality; he can afford to be a little more frivolous than his brother.
While he is adrift,
Harry is very close to his family.
His father, Charles, does everything he can to prevent him from completely sinking.
In fact, Charles is an excellent father.
When Harry begins to flirt dangerously with cannabis use,
He takes her to a rehabilitation center.
And Charles does this quite intelligently.
In fact, he's a more modern dad than you might think.
He is a very affectionate father and much more demonstrative than one might imagine.
After Diana's death, Charles tried to be a good father to Harry and William.
as they recently confided.
"Our dad, Charles, was there for two. He tried his best to replace mom and we will be eternally grateful to him."
Despite his father's support,
what will really save Harry,
It's about fulfilling one's childhood dream.
To become a soldier and serve the crown.
Unlike his brother, his university will be to go directly into the army.
The army was truly a lifesaver for him.
Suddenly, he had a use. He was a very good soldier.
And it is a catalyst that, all of a sudden, gives him a vocation.
The family will love it, his grandmother will love it.
Queen Elizabeth, who has a great fondness for the military.
And the queen comes to visit them and she goes past everyone and they're all like that, and Harry gives his grandmother a big smile, because she is his grandmother, after all.
Harry has only one idea in mind,
to do his country proud by going to fight in Afghanistan.
It was also a way for him to distance himself from his family and grow up; wanting to be away from his loved ones was a sign of maturity on his part.
It brought him a great deal.
His status as a prince of England requires him to have the government's permission, which he will obtain on one condition: to be there incognito.
He showed that he existed for his own worth, in fact.
Not simply because he has a title, not simply because he is a king's son, but because he is a soldier who fights, and who is respected by his comrades.
Surrounded by ordinary soldiers, Harry blossoms like never before.
But his secret identity will be discovered.
It will be revealed by an American website; his presence will be revealed there.
Overwhelmed by his global fame, he becomes a target.
Ultimately, he was a threat to the entire troop, because he could be the target of an attack or a kidnapping.
By remaining in Afghanistan, he is putting his life in danger and, consequently, the lives of the soldiers around him.
The government is having him urgently repatriated to England.
Deprived of the army, a lifebuoy, Harry experiences a new period of depression.
And it is his brother William who will finally allow him to overcome the psychological trauma of their mother's death.
Harry said it was William who helped him through his depressive periods.
who had told him to go see someone he shouldn't be ashamed of.
And today, when he realizes all the good it has done for him, he has decided with his brother and with Kate Middleton to get involved precisely in mental illness, in psychology, in talking, in verbalizing.
I've always thought that dwelling on the past is pointless, that it just makes you sadder, that's all.
It didn't change anything, it wouldn't bring Mom back. When you think like that, it's tragic.
You always told me that we should sit down and remember her, but at the time, I forced myself never to think about her.
While grieving,
Harry can finally rebuild his life and spread his wings.
Since the scandals and scandals, Harry has devoted his time to numerous charitable works, just as his mother did.
And very quickly, he became the most popular prince on the planet.
Harry, after all those difficult years, has finally become the most popular member of the royal family, even more so than the Queen. That's quite an achievement.
If Harry is now the darling of the English, it is mainly because he appears as the only true heir of Princess Diana, his mother.
Harry truly inherited Diana's magnetism, her ability to connect with people, her empathy.
He builds connections incredibly quickly.
He goes towards others, he dares to brave them, their security barriers, their metal barriers.
He dares to go to the people, to extend a hand to them.
He talks to people, he looks them in the eyes, he listens to them.
He won't hesitate to hug someone,
He will not hesitate to,
to reveal themselves to be truly very human.
A closeness to the people that one would not expect from a prince,
but that's what makes him the most normal man in the royal family.
Okay, fine, he's a prince, he knows it.
But he doesn't overdo it.
Harry is not a man who overdoes things.
Harry doesn't like royal protocol.
He likes it when people call him Harry, not sir.
So he's an ordinary man.
While Harry had always longed for a quiet life, far from the pomp and circumstance of the court palaces,
He has always shown a strong sense of duty.
He knows his place within the crown. He could have thrown it all away.
He could have run off a thousand times with a girl to the ends of the earth and said, "Here I am, I'm leaving."
He never did that.
He never forgot that he was a prince of England and that, as such, he had a role to play.
And Harry found his life's mission at the end of 2013 by accompanying wounded soldiers to the South Pole.
What's the point of all this?
It's about showing how impressed I am by these men.
They went through hell, and they came back from it.
And yet, they are still capable of achieving the unthinkable and returning, even injured.
Upon his return, to pay tribute to these extraordinary men, Harry will have a wonderful idea that will make his family proud.
This proves that anything is possible when you have the will.
Welcome to the game.
Welcome to the Invictus Games.
In 2014, he created the Invictus Games, a kind of Olympic Games for veterans and wounded in war.
I knew it was my duty to use my fame so that the whole world would recognize the spirit, and be inspired by the strength of those who once wore the uniform.
It's truly a charitable endeavor that he championed single-handedly. It's something that's very important to him.
He organizes them every year; he is very, very involved.
And from the moment he created the Invictus Games,
He has completely found his path and he is transformed.
He becomes an incredibly popular young man in the eyes of the public.
And that is one of his great achievements and something his mother would have been extraordinarily proud of.
Harry is so committed to the Invictus Games that he will achieve the unthinkable.
Bringing together two of the most inaccessible people in the world in a promotional spot.
Please, let's watch it together.
Yes.
Prince Harry, do you remember when you asked us to give our all at the Invictus Games?
Beware!
Seriously ?
He manages to convince Barack and Michelle Obama, the most powerful president in the world no less, to appear in a video where he features himself, and even more impressively, he manages to convince his grandmother, Elizabeth II.
This is unprecedented.
Harry clearly has the magic formula.
Clearly, you are facing him.
He tells you, come on, let's go, it's good.
And in fact, we can't say no, it's impossible.
Friends of the stars, adored by the people, dedicated to causes,
Harry has everything going for him.
He's a great charmer.
I have to say, I think he looks very handsome with his slightly reddish hair like that. I've always thought he was very handsome.
In 2016, at the age of 32, he was even voted the sexiest prince on the planet.
There are plenty of photos that show him as athletic.
in full possession of his faculties, sometimes shirtless.
It stirred up some fantasies, let's say.
Young women all over the world dream of only one thing: marrying Harry and becoming a princess.
He receives marriage proposals, passionate declarations,
because he really is the most eligible bachelor on the planet.
Despite its success with women's rims,
Harry can't seem to keep his girlfriends.
who all end up leaving him
incapable of assuming the role of a princess.
There was too much pressure on his daughters; they weren't ready to face the press and the pressure of royal duties. So ultimately, they couldn't handle it.
Each time, they told themselves, no, me, joining the firm, as the royal family is nicknamed, is not for me.
These are painful separations for Prince Harry, who, in private, dreams of only one thing,
to find the woman of his life and start a family.
He's been saying for a very long time that he wants to have a dog, that he wants to have children,
that he wants to have...
this calm, affectionate, and warm life.
Each time, in a certain way, he believed it.
Harry suffered quite a bit from this lack of affection.
the lack of having a girlfriend,
a bride-to-be by his side.
Two years ago, when Prince Harry no longer believed in it,
He will finally find true love.
The story of Meghan Markle.
It is the story of a mixed-race Cinderella who was never destined to marry a prince.
Meghan comes from a fairly modest background.
She is anything but the young girl who was raised to one day become the companion of one of the princes of England, quite the contrary.
She went through some difficult years.
Born into poverty, Meghan grew up in the most criminal slums of Los Angeles, where gangs and drug dealers held sway.
Meghan Markle wasn't born with a silver spoon in her mouth.
He really is someone who comes from a very, very simple background.
Her mother is a social worker and yoga teacher.
His father is a lighting technician on TV series.
Meghan wasn't born in Beverly Hills.
She comes, therefore, from a fairly average family, not to say quite modest.
His father is white and of Irish descent.
Her mother is black, African-American,
And we often learn about it because of our nanny.
Every day, when she left her house,
Meghan is facing racism.
It's not easy being mixed race.
We are not white, we are not black, we are in between, and as a result, we don't always feel very well accepted in one community or the other.
At school...
She says that she was asked to tick a form which said: "Are you white? Are you black?" and that she didn't know.
There's no box for her.
Insults and humiliations,
Far from discouraging Meghan, they will forge her character.
At 12 years old, shocked by a sexist advertisement for dishwashing liquid,
She decides to go to war against the brand.
The women struggle with the dirty dishes and pots.
I don't think it's good for children to grow up thinking that their mother should do everything.
It's always...
"Mommy does this, mommy does that."
She wrote to the whole world, she wrote to Hillary Clinton, she wrote to every influential person in the government.
And she won her case.
Meghan succeeded in getting the advertisement slogan changed.
An achievement that earned him television accolades.
Everyone is battling against dirty dishes and pots and pans.
If you notice something you don't like or that shocks you,
whether it's television or elsewhere,
Write letters, and send them to the right people.
You will succeed in making a difference, not just for yourself, but for everyone.
We can see directly the strength of character of this young woman, and that she is not just a pretty young girl, but someone who has a lot of follow-through and a real vocation.
Meghan will also be the first in her family to obtain a university degree.
She will truly, from a very young age,
to be marked, characterized by ambition.
She wants to succeed.
From a very young age, Meghan accompanied her father to film sets.
From then on, she had only one goal,
to become an actress and conquer Hollywood.
However, his first auditions turned into a fiasco.
When she was looking for roles, it was difficult for her to find a place because she was mixed race, we didn't really know how to categorize her.
She is in between, she is half white, half black.
She said, "I was never black enough to play black roles and never white enough to play white roles."
Meghan is not giving up on her dream.
His determination took the form of an inner struggle.
In 2011, she finally landed a role tailor-made for her in the series Suits.
She plays Rachel Zane, a legal student who dreams of becoming a lawyer but is convinced she lacks the necessary skills.
Her character is sexy and mixed-race, like her, with one exception.
In the series, Rachel's father is black and her mother is white.
She has a very sparkling role, she is pretty, she is friendly, she is dynamic, and she is ultra sexy.
For the purposes of the series filmed in Canada, Meghan moved to Toronto.
At the time, she was married to a television producer, Trevor Engelson.
But their union only lasted 2 years.
A romantic setback, from which the young woman recovers very quickly because her popularity explodes.
Congratulations, Suits is the number 1 TV series.
Thank you, that's incredible.
She has almost 2 million followers on Instagram.
She has a lot of fans, she walks the red carpet. That's it, she's a star.
Meghan's life was about to change dramatically in July 2016.
While on holiday in London, she is invited to dinner at a very chic Soho club by one of her friends who wants to introduce her to someone.
It was a blind date, something really arranged by a mutual friend.
That evening, Megan's suitor was Prince Harry.
the most eligible bachelor on the planet.
The first question she asked when she was told she was going to meet Prince Harry was, "Is he nice?"
It's hard to believe that this is the only thing she asked about him.
Obviously, meeting a prince is exciting for any girl who says to herself, "Becoming a princess, yes of course, we all want the crown jewels."
Harry immediately falls under the spell of the American star.
He said it was love at first sight. He thought to himself, "I'm really going to have to improve on this one because she's very, very good."
Very quickly, Harry became extremely determined in his desire to seduce Meghan, bombarding her with messages.
At 35, Meghan has already had some love affairs.
She is not ready to throw herself into the arms of just anyone, even if he were a prince.
She let him insist. She really needed to play the role of the desired and coveted girl. It was Harry who had to win over his shepherdess, not the other way around.
To enjoy their budding relationship in complete secrecy,
The two lovers will isolate themselves on the other side of the world.
He invited her to join him in Botswana, Africa, for five days.
as his brother had done with Kate, incidentally.
They spent 5 days away from gilded splendor and palaces, trekking without electricity and without comfort.
Harry and Meghan are getting to know each other in a very natural way.
Even though they don't come from the same world,
They will find they have many things in common, including their parents' divorce.
They both grew up with parents who,
For a time, they were torn apart, then separated.
And that's something that, in my opinion, allows them to...
to create an intimate bond between them from the very first moments.
But what will captivate Harry most of all,
It's because Meghan is a committed woman.
with values, like him.
Now is the time to dig wells and improve living conditions here.
Meghan does not hesitate to travel the world to defend causes that are close to her heart.
such as the installation of drinking water in a village in Rwanda.
He found someone completely different, who has a social soul and political convictions.
If she had only been a TV star, that wouldn't have been enough. That's what appealed to Harry.
Wherever she goes, Meghan makes her voice heard, such as at the UN for women's equality.
I am proud to be a woman, and a feminist.
Images and values ​​that remind Harry of the struggles of his mother, the People's Princess.
He saw someone who had more in common with his mother, at least in terms of idealism and political causes.
With her background, Meghan has everything to fascinate the general public.
For the first time in the royal family, we will have a young woman who has experienced this in her life, in her own flesh.
difficult things like racism, poverty, and social struggles.
Meghan Markle could well become the new star of the Windsor dynasty.
In record time, Meghan, the very sexy American star, has managed the feat of dethroning the very English and impeccable Kate Middleton in the hearts of photographers.
Kate, who has been the number one media personality in the royal family in recent years,
She is truly relegated to the background.
Kate has been in the circuit for 15 years, I think we all know who she is.
She's suddenly become quite outdated because of Meghan Markle, because she's been demoted. Meghan represents modernity, she's much more rock 'n' roll.
A situation that could end up annoying Kate Middleton.
She who has done so much for the image of the royal family.
Kate must maintain her position.
And it's not easy with someone new arriving.
Meghan must be exasperating Kate a little bit because she finds her too American.
not quite fitting the mold of a future princess.
For now, the official version is that Kate is delighted by Meghan's arrival in the family.
But... Is this reality?
What do you think of the engagement announcement?
William and I are thrilled. This is wonderful news. It's a very exciting time for a couple. I congratulate them and hope they enjoy every moment.
Meghan and Kate seem to get along very well.
Meghan is experiencing a bit of what Kate went through, so she gives her a lot of advice.
To silence the rumors, it is said that behind the scenes, Kate even went so far as to coach Meghan on her future role as princess.
Meghan has already said that Kate helped her a lot. Initially, she explained to me what to expect, what might surprise me. And she says that made her life much easier at the beginning.
In terms of protocol, Kate has nothing to worry about.
Meghan is still far from being on her level, particularly when it comes to curtsying to the Queen.
as we saw during his first Christmas.
There's Kate, who does a fairly normal curtsy, by the standards.
And then we see that, Meghan...
She did something rather haphazardly, like that.
Fairly quick, shipped.
without conviction.
For the American actress, this public bow was a first.
She has lived in the United States for 35 years; for them, reverence is a joke.
So it can be learned.
There was still a little bit of work to be done on the curtsy, where Kate Middleton is a model of the genre.
While Kate and Meghan display a deliberate display of close friendship at official events,
Rumors are circulating that the two women will never be true friends.
It's certain that they have...
They are separated by an ocean. They come from two different worlds.
They are two parallel worlds, after all.
One is formatted for,
the other,
That wasn't part of the plan.
Everything sets Kate, the commoner destined to be a princess, apart from Meghan, the feminist from the rough neighborhoods of Los Angeles.
I don't think Kate and Meghan had that much in common.
between an American actress and an English woman,
who doesn't do much else besides being a prince's wife.
Kate, today, is the perfect family woman, a little too polished, what does her daily life consist of? Taking care of her children 100%, getting involved in a few causes, but you can tell that she is not as passionate a woman as Meghan can be when it comes to defending causes.
The press has already run headlines about the sisters-in-law war, betting on the rise of rivalries between the two young women.
How will they manage?
That's really the big question mark.
That's what's going to be exciting to follow.
They have every interest in getting along well,
to ensure harmony,
And above all, there must be no leaks to the press saying there's rivalry, because then...
It's a selling point, but for them, it would be a bit of a devastating problem.
That makes me laugh, there won't be any rivalry.
Faced with the weight of the crown,
The only two commoner princesses in the royal family might instead choose to join forces.
I think they are already very aware that it's about union,
peace between them
who will save them.
Kate is intelligent enough, and I think Meghan is too, so in the long run it will work out extremely well.
It would even seem that Kate is delighted to share the pressure.
Kate is very happy to have support. She is glad to have someone with whom to share the responsibilities of being a member of the royal family.
There, she has an ally.
Having been in the public eye for 15 years, Kate would not be unhappy with a little media respite, to enjoy her third child in complete discretion.
Kate Middleton's first two pregnancies were an unprecedented media frenzy, particularly the birth of Prince George, it's true, but we experienced some of the same scenes of hysteria.
Perhaps the arrival of Meghan and Harry as a married couple within this royal family will allow Kate to have that degree of withdrawal which will allow her to take care of and devote herself 100% to her children.
Since she started dating Prince Harry, Meghan Markle has become the number one attraction in England.
On September 25th, a year after their incredible whirlwind romance, Prince Harry and Meghan Markle finally made their love story official at the Invictus Games in Toronto.
It was a very well-organized entrance.
with an almost perfect choreography so that she would arrive with him.
Meghan herself chose a very unconventional outfit. She arrived in ripped jeans with sunglasses and a boyfriend shirt.
In this first appearance, Meghan already established her style.
This is a far cry from the hyper-protocolary codes to which Kate Middleton adheres.
But the couple didn't stop there.
It's unprecedented for an unmarried member of the royal family to dare to kiss his partner at an official event.
Not only did they hold hands, which is very rare for a royal couple, they kissed; it was an image that surprised everyone.
We knew right away that it was serious.
You can feel that there is a true, sincere love.
She's here at the Invictus Games, she's happy to be with her boyfriend.
Starting with the Invictus Games, Meghan Markle became in one evening the target of a global media frenzy that would never cease.
Media outlets around the world are rushing to find out more about this young girl.
Who is she? What does she look like? What is her daily life like?
The paparazzi are obviously chasing her, just like Kate Middleton did back then.
And she becomes the target of attack.
Anything goes when it comes to selling.
Because this is the first time a prince from the royal family has had a relationship with a mixed-race woman.
And yet...
This simple love will awaken old racist sentiments.
Obviously, the fact that she is mixed race has fueled many conversations. For example, is this normal? Is this permissible?
Is this good or bad for the royal bloodline? We are really hearing reactions, which include racist remarks.
The worst horrors are circulating.
Meghan is even accused of threatening the British monarchy.
There was even, remember,
Far-right politicians have said that Meghan's engagement to Prince Harry will tarnish the royal family. So it's gone very, very far.
Although used to gossip and fake news, the young actress will also have to face outlandish accusations coming from her own family.
She has a half-sister who is hateful to the extreme, who honestly is overflowing with jealousy of Meghan's success, and who has said the worst possible and imaginable horrors.
However, 17 years separate the two women who have never lived together.
Samantha Grant, who said quite plainly, "she always dreamed of becoming a princess, she had pictures of Prince Harry."
In short, you know, she's an opportunist, she's an ambitious woman ready to do anything to get there.
In the coming weeks, she is preparing to release a book which will be simply titled "Confessions of the Sister of a Future Ambitious Princess".
So, all of England is already, in a way, waiting to read this famous book.
Meghan sells.
The English tabloids are having a field day also unpacking the story of his half-brother.
Thomas Markle Jr. went to prison last year after holding a gun to his girlfriend's head. So, they're a rather colorful family.
Harry is outraged by the attacks his girlfriend has suffered.
From the beginning, Harry understood that there was a danger to Meghan.
And Prince Harry cannot stand it.
This media lynching painfully reminds him of the one his mother experienced.
He remembers very, very well how much of a burden it must have been for his mother, for Diana.
And he refuses to let his partner carry the weight.
Furious, Harry releases an official statement demanding an end to the racist and sexist attacks against his girlfriend.
An extremely firm, extremely outraged reaction when Meghan was attacked on social media and in the press.
It was unprecedented.
He said: "You stop, you're talking nonsense. It's not true. She's my girlfriend, my future wife.
So you accept and you stop."
Through his statements,
Harry is subtly preparing public opinion and his family for the announcement of his engagement.
But he's missing just one agreement, and the most important one,
that of his grandmother, the queen.
Please sit down.
I think the Queen must have been preparing herself for the idea that Harry would, after all, dare to do something different.
And the queen gave her approval for a foreigner, a television actress, it's really exceptional, it's unprecedented in the royal family.
If the Queen agrees to admit into the royal family a young, mixed-race, divorced American woman,
It's because she learned from the failed marriage of Charles and Diana.
Elisabeth finally understood that there was nothing to be done.
A love match,
Ultimately, it's the only thing we can believe in, because an arranged marriage always ends up falling apart.
Finally, on November 27, 2017, Harry and Meghan officially announced their engagement.
This was an opportunity for the couple to reveal the scenario of the marriage proposal.
It was an evening like any other.
A quiet evening. What were we doing? We were cooking a chicken.
Finally, we tried.
Yes, to roast a chicken. I wasn't expecting that.
It was so cute and natural.
Very romantic.
And that's when he went down on one knee.
A marriage proposal that was ultimately quite ordinary for a prince like Harry.
Obviously, this way of telling the story makes us think, "Oh, but actually, they're so simple, so like us."
We think Harry is a normal prince, but to propose in front of a roast chicken, like that on a Sunday evening at Kensington Palace, it's true that it's a little less dreamy, we're a little disappointed by his marriage proposal.
On the other hand, the engagement ring that Prince Harry gave to Meghan is unique and priceless for several reasons.
The main stone comes from Botswana.
and the small diamonds around it come from my mother's jewelry collection.
To make sure she accompanies us on this incredible adventure.
Obviously, Harry also wanted to involve his mother in this very important moment of his life.
The two smaller stones that encircle this large diamond are stones that come from a brooch that Lady Diana wore on her wedding day.
Finally, Prince Harry insisted on designing the ring himself.
It's magnificent and he drew it himself, it's amazing.
I still think that when you're the royal family and you have gigantic emeralds, I find it petty.
By agreeing to become a princess,
Meghan must first give up her old life, starting with her acting career, which she spent years building.
She has clearly ended her contract with the series that made her famous, Suits.
She was an actress, and overnight she could no longer be one.
Even more difficult, for a woman of character like Meghan Markle, she must also sacrifice her freedom of expression.
Meghan Markle will never be able to vote, will never be able to speak publicly on politics, religion, or money matters.
She can no longer have a blog, no social media, no Facebook account, all of that has been deleted.
The royal family does not have the right.
She cleared the decks in order to take on the new role she will have within the royal family.
Meghan Markle, a Catholic, had to convert.
She was baptized on March 6th in a secret ceremony.
To join the ranks of the Windsors, one must necessarily be of the Anglican religion, since Elizabeth II is the head of the Anglican Church.
These were radical changes that Meghan accepted willingly and out of love, as she recently revealed in an interview.
I don't see these as renunciations, but simply as changes.
This is a new challenge.
A new chapter begins.
Even having managed to overcome everything in his life, his main challenge now... is to manage to comply with the rules of the most rigid royalty in the world.
It's surely the most cumbersome monarchy there is today. It's a monarchy where you still have all those uniforms, you have the real crown on your head.
It is a very strict monarchy in terms of rules.
Whereas Harry, by birth, was raised with a protocol that he has mastered perfectly,
Meghan, for her part, must flawlessly apply the codes and requirements of the British aristocracy, a world that is completely unknown to her.
The protocol is something difficult to learn.
A future member of the royal family doesn't take selfies with the crowd.
does not give autographs,
She always wears a pair of tights under her skirts.
Very short dresses and plunging necklines are a thing of the past.
Old-fashioned European educational rules, absurd and outdated for an American.
And yet...
A person who is to enter the royal family does not cross their legs but puts them side by side.
She must always stand at least three steps behind the Queen, and she must curtsy to Elizabeth II.
To be able to maintain her status, Meghan is constantly accompanied by a personal assistant who worked for Kate Middleton.
This lady's role is now to teach Meghan everything that is and is not done in terms of royal protocol.
Megan can also count on Harry's 33 years of experience.
Prince Harry is also helping her.
He said, laughing, that he makes diagrams for her so she can keep track of all the uncles, aunts, and cousins.
That he accompany her in everything she needs to know.
Despite all these efforts, the young American woman will make numerous missteps with each new public appearance.
So, as a result, her reflex is to accept a selfie, an autograph, or even a hug from a fan who asks for it.
But all of that is strictly forbidden by the British royal family.
Never, ever has Kate Middleton broken protocol to this extent.
It's different.
It's a change from the usual monarchical rigidity.
Well, why not?
People clearly like it.
Protocol blunders that could well become Meghan Markle's trademark.
She must, of course, be a worthy representative of the Windsor family.
But alongside that, she must not forget what she once was.
And then, she also needs to clearly distinguish herself from Kate from the very beginning.
Although they love them, the British demand exemplary behavior from their prince.
Meghan Markle is joining a family where, 365 days a year, 24 hours a day, even on vacation, all over the world and for her entire life, she will be scrutinized and spied on.
And nothing will ever be spared him again.
I think she must be super in love, because to follow all those rules, it must be complicated on a daily basis.
You need to have a lot of character, and above all, quite a bit of courage.
Of course, there is the palace life, the luxury, the castles, the beautiful dresses and the parties.
But by marrying a prince, Meghan will also have duties.
It will also be a difficult life, where one will have to attend to obligations that are sometimes very heavy.
We have to hold social events constantly.
We should look at people and be interested in their problems, even though we might not care about them.
Meghan will also have to bear the weight of the crown.
We are with a man who doesn't do what he wants, and therefore we are the wife of someone who doesn't do what he wants, so we don't do what we want.
It's something that truly is a deprivation of liberty that few young women can tolerate. The label is truly akin to a prison.
In return, Meghan Markle gains media visibility that she would never have had access to before meeting Harry.
She will be much better known through her marriage to Prince Harry than through her series Suits, and her Instagram account.
And she also has enough consistency to say to herself, okay, I'm going to have a new life, I'm going to use this extraordinary platform that is the royal family, to change things, to change the world, which has been her true desire since her earliest childhood.
She can tell herself that I am still contributing to the modernization of this family, namely the marriage between a prince and a mixed-race person.
Harry and Meghan,
It is the story of a true story, that of the prince and the shepherdess.
But will they manage to eclipse the star couple of the royal family, Kate and William?
On Monday, April 23, following the same ceremony and for centuries, Buckingham Palace announced the birth of a prince of England.
Framed, an official statement is presented to the public on a gilded easel.
It was only after the announcement made by the Queen's office that William was able to visit his two children, George and Charlotte, with their new little brother, Louis.
An hour later, and in front of cameras from all over the world,
The Duke and Duchess of Cambridge finally presented their third child, Louis, to an expected crowd.
With the day of hospitalization costing British taxpayers 7000 euros, to everyone's surprise, Kate only stayed at the clinic for 7 hours for her delivery.
And as usual, she appeared impeccably groomed and made up, as if nothing had happened.
Very happy, delighted, thank you. Three, three times more worried now.
Kate and William have always projected the image of a perfect couple.
They are young, they are beautiful.
Their first two children, George and Charlotte, are already stars.
Charlotte, Charlotte, come and pet the dog.
Kate and William's life is like a fairy tale.
And yet...
It makes for a rather bland couple. It makes for a rather boring couple, "boring" as the English say.
Yes, it's too "goody-goody".
How am I going to translate "goody-goody"? It's too much of a model of virtue.
She's always smiling. I would have said it's perfect for the queen.
But it can annoy people after a while.
They don't want to be interesting.
They want to live their lives and take on the task that will be theirs when the time comes.
Behind the forced smiles, it's even whispered that while William is doing the bare minimum,
The truth is, he dreads the day when he will have to lead the same life as his grandmother, the queen.
The Queen, on January 1st of each year,
knows that she will be on her schedule until December 31st of the year, quarter hour by quarter hour.
That is to say, she doesn't have a day to herself to do nothing, to dream, everything is codified.
It's hell.
Does William really want to be king?
William is ready to be king. Would he want to be? We cannot decide, but he has been prepared for this role.
None of the members of the royal family wished to be members of the royal family.
None of the members of the royal family envy being king.
It is said that he did not want to be, except that he has no choice, just as Prince Charles has no choice either.
William is not yet ready to take on such a demanding role.
It is an immense violence against an individual to be unable to express a single opinion throughout their life.
You are expected to embody an ethic, a philosophy,
that you give an example.
Behind the scenes, what keeps Prince William going is the unwavering support of Kate, who always stands by his side.
"She is my balance," he said.
"She is the person who will make me a good king one day," he recently declared in the pages of an English magazine.
Kate is perfect too.
On every occasion, she proves herself worthy of the royal family.
It is a blessing for the royal family to have found a young girl who loves so much, who takes on this responsibility with such pleasure.
I would even go further, there is an English expression, we say "she does the job", she does the job.
And above all, she never makes any protocol blunders.
She didn't make a mistake; it's very difficult, it requires constant attention to reach that level of perfection.
For her, it's natural. That, I think, is the key to her success.
It must be said that, unlike Diana,
Kate has been conditioned her whole life to become a princess.
Kate was prepared for a very long time. They wanted to test her willpower, their determination, her moral strength.
It's not for nothing that the English press nicknamed Kate Middleton "Waity Katie", meaning the one who waits.
She fell in love with William when she was 20, and it took her 10 years to marry him, so I think she understood the role.
"The task ahead of me is very daunting,
But I'm taking it all in stride.
William is a very good teacher, he helps me a lot.
And I'm looking forward to spending even more time with him."
"She really knows how to flatter me."
With Kate, the monarchy gains a model princess, who is also a fashion icon.
All the magazines are vying to put her on the cover.
Kate looks stunning, she has style.
She has style, she has class, she is always elegant.
She has a body that can carry anything, a bit like Diana back in the day.
Kate is absolutely a fashion icon.
Kate is a favorite with the press.
but not only that.
It should be noted that every dress, every blazer, every pair of shoes, whether they be ballet flats or stilettos worn by Kate Middleton, are snapped up the day after her appearance by young English women who really want to copy this style.
The princess stimulates the British economy with each of her appearances.
She manages to sell absolutely everything she touches, like few other women in the world.
Her best-selling items, all her maternity dresses, and the outfit she wore for her engagement.
She is wearing a blue dress, sold out; no more blue dresses of this type were available.
An impeccable style, which sells, but lacks a bit of imagination.
By trying so hard to please the queen, Kate is starting to resemble her.
The queen is already very, very colorful.
You need sunglasses to look at it.
The colors the queen is wearing are indeed in very bad taste.
And I think Kate is starting to slip into that same bad taste.
And behind the glossy images,
The princess is missing a bit of spice.
Kate is not a pop princess at all.
It is also,
a very serious personality
or even a little faded.
Kate is someone who is, let's say, a bit like clockwork.
Everyone needs to be able to project a certain idea of ​​England onto her, and the best way to achieve that is to avoid showing too strong a personality.
Since the beginning of their relationship, Kate and William have made a flawless run at every major stage of their lives.
They are perfect.
William is the perfect future king. Apart from his hair loss, he's perfect.
And with her, there's never a misstep.
On April 29, 2011, the couple gave the British public the most exceptional wedding of all time.
It's a breath of fresh air. It's the prince, the princess, the crown of England, the castle.
The long train, the tiara, the diamonds, it's a dream.
There were almost 3 billion viewers gathered in front of their screens. So it was a love story that was absolutely moving the entire world.
All the ingredients for the perfect marriage are there.
Famous guests included Elton John and the Beckham couple.
A simple yet majestic decoration.
A bride and groom radiating happiness.
William and Kate represent a sincere love, a true love.
They chose each other.
They brought a breath of fresh air, let's be clear.
They were both beautiful, it was very well done.
By joining the Windsor dynasty, Kate, the commoner, is realizing her dream.
Catherine Elisabeth, do you want to take this man as your husband?
Yes, I want it.
Kate, all her life, prepared for the big day; in her fantasies, in her head, that's what she wanted.
She knows it, her dress makes people forget the one Diana wore at her wedding in 1981.
It's a white dress with lots of lace, it clings to her skin, it's by Alexander McQueen.
The dress was amazing, the train was absolutely gorgeous.
Kate had planned everything for a grand arrival.
With one small exception.
The overly perfect bride is going to have the spotlight stolen by her sister and her white sheath dress.
First of all, it's not Kate who's putting on the show, it's her sister.
When you see Pipa in her dress, streamlined like a fighter jet,
I must say that all the networks in the world were surprised.
David Lowe, a television commentator, immediately sensed that Pipa and her swayback would capture all the media attention.
I was the first person in the world to talk about Pipa's buttocks.
I was told to be quiet through my earpiece.
that one shouldn't talk about things like that.
Pipa's hip-swaying will make the front page of all the newspapers.
I was congratulated because we got the whole world talking about Pipa's buttocks, which were sexier anyway.
There was a slight movement of the hips.
Kate will find solace on the balcony of Buckingham Palace.
The princely couple offers their subjects not a,
But two kisses, a sign of his sincere love.
I told the people who were on set, you'll see, he's going to kiss her again.
And sure enough, in the next second they kissed a second time.
I found it incredibly charming.
After the perfect wedding,
three births, two boys and one girl.
With the king's choice, the future of the crown is assured.
They had the children when it was necessary.
The heir has been born, he is even a little boy, so there will not even be a conflict over whether there will be a king or a queen.
Everything fits perfectly within the frame, within the mold.
Children already resembling their parents,
well-dressed, well-behaved and always smiling.
They are very attentive to the proper education of their children, to the fact that they must be,
Definitely not spoiled or arrogant,
which could happen quite quickly given their notoriety and privileges.
William and Kate prefer evenings with their families by the fire to protocol obligations.
William and Kate spend a lot of time with their family. They enjoy eating pizza in front of the television, like many people do. It's a fairly ordinary family life.
It doesn't look very exciting, but at the same time, I think they have the life of old young people.
They are 35 years old, have 3 children, and seem very happy.
In their private lives, they primarily want peace, a happiness, in quotes, like everyone else.
They invented a new style, which was monarchical simplicity.
An ordinary daily life that greatly annoys the media, who are absolutely determined to find flaws in this couple, who seem so perfect in all circumstances.
The press is on the lookout for any small misstep in order to create a soap opera around this couple.
Kate Middleton is going to give a French newspaper its scoop of the year 2012.
She had been photographed with a telephoto lens, topless, while she was resting on private property.
The photo is going viral.
The couple sued the newspaper and won their case.
The French magazine was fined 45,000 euros.
And there you have it, it certainly makes an impression.
Since then, the press has been content to criticize Kate for her thinness and to question strange cuts on her hands.
When the press noted that Kate Middleton regularly had bandages on her fingers,
She began to wonder if she might not be...
as Diana might have been, bulimic.
Because to make yourself vomit, you put your fingers at the back of your throat, and isn't that what hurt her?
That's all it takes for journalists to conclude that Kate is just as unhappy as Diana and suffers from the same eating disorders.
As for William, there's nothing particularly juicy to report.
The worst thing the prince is criticized for is not being involved enough in the affairs of the crown.
Moreover, he has been heavily criticized for his lack of appearances.
People said that William was a little bit lazy.
Hello, pleased to meet you.
Delighted.
Since becoming a father, William only fulfills about a hundred official duties, whereas his grandmother fulfills more than 300.
It was found that he didn't have enough engagements per year, which was honestly true. He had far fewer than Prince Charles, far fewer than his grandparents, who are 91 and 95 years old respectively.
The only stolen images of William date back to March 2017.
The prince was filmed letting loose on the dance floor of a nightclub in Switzerland.
We have these images of him dancing, partying.
That's great, we really, really want to use them in the media.
And even going so far as to start a story about "doesn't he get bored with Kate Middleton?"
In the end, nothing too scandalous.
What we see of them are the moments when they are particularly upright and strict.
But we certainly hope that behind closed doors, they too know how to party and live the life of a couple in their thirties like any other.
While the British people are fond of modern-day fairy tales, they also need escapades and scandals.
One royal couple chases another, as long as they provide a spectacle concerning her gracious majesty.
So, since the announcement of their engagement, Meghan and Harry have totally eclipsed the too-polished and too-perfect William and Kate.
Kate and William, they are more reserved, more rigid, more boring all the same.
Attention is now focused on
Harry and Meghan because they are new, because they are the future.
William and Kate, it's already a done deal.
So this year, despite the birth of Kate's third child, it's going to be the year of Harry and Meghan.
By their simplicity and relaxed manner, Meghan and Harry appear more modern and more fun, in a word, less boring.
The public was just waiting for this.
They are quite a scandalous couple.
Very handsome, young, dynamic.
We see them kissing with Harry, and so on. Everything we've never seen between Kate and William.
They laugh, they hold hands.
A breath of fresh air. That's what's attractive, I think, to people.
Despite their different styles, both couples have every reason to get along.
because William and Harry have been inseparable since their mother's death in '97.
It is truly this tragedy that will unbreakably bind them together.
It is said that they do not go a day without calling each other, sometimes even several times a day.
William and Harry are extremely close, extremely in sync.
William always protected his little brother and vice versa.
I don't think there's any jealousy between them.
There is no competition between them, but on the contrary, there is a strong sense of solidarity which is important for a monarchy.
They were determined not to let a woman jeopardize their close relationship.
I'm scaring you.
And when William congratulates his brother on his marriage, naturally,
He does it in a very ironic way.
Personally, I hope this means he'll stay away from my fridge and stop stealing all my food, like he has for the past few years.
To put an end to all rumors of rivalry or jealousy between their partners,
The two brothers have a solution.
all four of them make appearances.
Kate, Harry and I are delighted to be here this morning, and to launch our first Royal Foundation forum with Meghan.
The word is that the four of them get along well.
They do a lot of things together, and very quickly at that.
Kate was the first person who met Meghan from the family with William.
They have great trust in each other, this whole little quartet.
A royal quartet that already has a nickname,
the "Fab Four", in reference to the nickname the four Beatles had.
The two couples have also chosen to share the immense Kensington Palace.
Obviously, Diana's residence, therefore, is linked to childhood memories for Harry and William.
to many things that mattered to them.
And besides, they like being together, so Kate, William, Harry and Meghan will be neighbors.
It is in this place steeped in family history that Harry and Meghan will write their future, with or without children.
Meghan is not like Kate, bound by the duty to provide heirs to the monarchy.
The Crown already has George and Charlotte, so they have virtually no institutional need to have children.
So they can do whatever they want.
But the question on everyone's mind is:
Will Meghan be able to handle the pressure? And will Harry be the faithful husband she imagines?
Meghan is a mix of Diana and Kate together.
So it's possible that it will go very, very well.
Or it's possible that things might go a little less well.
The life of a princess means being cheated on pretty quickly.
Because Harry was a big womanizer until not long ago.
And Meghan, she's not going to tolerate him cheating on her.
Already, some observers are betting on the failure of their union.
They seem too different to get along well.
Perhaps it's the magic of the encounter, I don't know.
But if it holds up, it'll be fun.
Time will tell if this marriage is as solid as it seems.
Meanwhile, Diana's two sons have found happiness under the watchful eye of their grandmother, Elisabeth.
The Queen is very encouraging towards her grandsons' campaigns.
She is protective.
She believes it's important that they have time to build a very strong family unit. Therefore, she wisely welcomes these stepdaughters with great kindness and creates the conditions for their success.
The only downside is that a new battle could break out between the couples.
Which one will be the most popular?
If Harry and Meghan ever...
who are, nevertheless, cooler, warmer, and more approachable in appearance,
attract more people and more press,
Well, it could still become a bit of a problem for the royalty after a while.
Today, the match is already over.
Meghan and Harry win the prize for glamour, naturalness and simplicity.
A stance that will go with the uprightness and spotless perfection displayed by the couple William and Kate.
I trust Kate and William to strategically,
choose a few events that will make people talk about them.
And I also trust Harry and Meghan to step down when the time is right.
Everything is calculated.
Life is a long journey.
And I think that in the end, the winners will still be Kate and William.
Kate and William,
Meghan and Harry,
or the story of a fairy tale.
A story where two little girls from the common people fell in love with young and handsome orphaned princes.
But let us hope that, as in fairy tales,
They loved each other,
They lived happily ever after and had many children.